<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tyler Rouze</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tyler Rouze</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
    <title>My Recent dbt Community Spotlight!</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/dbt-community-spotlight/</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/dbt-community-spotlight/</guid>
    <description>
        &lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/dbt_nyc.jpg&#34;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I recently had the honor of being featured on dbt Labs&amp;rsquo; community spotlight! You can read more about it &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.getdbt.com/community/spotlight/tyler-rouze&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been an absolute pleasure to be a part of this community for a few years now. I&amp;rsquo;ve said it before during my talks, but working in data, especially in our space pushing the boundaries and defining what best practices should be, is difficult work. It&amp;rsquo;s a common trope, but most of the world&amp;rsquo;s data goes unanalyzed, and that means there&amp;rsquo;s so much more we can learn about our world if we&amp;rsquo;re able to effectively process and analyze it. Fundamentally, I believe that&amp;rsquo;s what many of us are trying to do in the &amp;ldquo;Modern Data Stack&amp;rdquo; space. We&amp;rsquo;ve come a long way, but have a long ways to go in terms of settling on best in breed developer tools and workflows. It&amp;rsquo;s only through collaboration and the willingness to be vulnerable and share what we&amp;rsquo;re working on that we can continue to move this community forward, and I&amp;rsquo;m glad to be a part of it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As always, if you want to talk data with me, use any one of the links on my &lt;a href=&#34;https://tylerrouze.com&#34;&gt;homepage&lt;/a&gt; to get in touch the way you prefer.&lt;/p&gt;

    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
    <title>5 Steps to Optimize your dbt Implementation</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/dbt-healthcheck-webinar/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/dbt-healthcheck-webinar/</guid>
    <description>
        &lt;p&gt;I recently took the opportunity to speak to clients of Analytics8 about keeping their data transformation practices up to date through periodic health checks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&#34;766&#34; height=&#34;431&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ltio6psFpNs?si=ePtOCfIBHCTzIVIn&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
    <title>Recap: My First Marathon</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/austin-marathon/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/austin-marathon/</guid>
    <description>
        &lt;div class=&#34;strava-embed-placeholder&#34; data-embed-type=&#34;activity&#34; data-embed-id=&#34;10788543034&#34; data-style=&#34;standard&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;script src=&#34;https://strava-embeds.com/embed.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
    <title>I ran my first half-marathon!</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/3m-half/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2024 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/3m-half/</guid>
    <description>
        &lt;p&gt;About five months ago, I started my first training block ever to run a long distance race.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think it is a common experience for many who grow up playing team sports to view running as a punishment. Missed your free throws? Run lines. Got blown out on your home field? Next practice, we&amp;rsquo;re running. The crazy thing is, I even ran cross country for a time growing up, but even then, that was about running a race to &lt;em&gt;beat&lt;/em&gt; people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A weird thing happens as you get older. They say you have the vast majority of your novel experiences in the first 25 years of your life. After that, time starts to move pretty quickly because you are simply just used to the world around you. It is with this truth that finding enjoyment in the mundane becomes a focus. Running, for me, has become one of those mundanities. There is something about the steady pounding of the pavement to a beat that just puts you into a meditative state. The day&amp;rsquo;s stresses fade away for the time being, and the only thing that truly matters is taking that next step.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I originally set out to run this race as my first long distance event, which it was, but I did not anticipate feeling good enough to run 13 miles in a single session about a month into what would be a just shy of a five month training block (I was starting from zero, thus the extended length of the block!). As is common in the marathoning business, this race became earmarked as a tuneup of sorts instead, a marker on my progress towards what would become my new goal, running my first full marathon.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The progress has been steady, but in the thick of a training block where I have been quickly adapting to faster paces and longer distances (faster than anticipated), going into this race I really had no idea what my potential might be. The 3M Half Marathon in Austin, Texas is well known as a fast course. Starting north of the city and heading into the river valley downtown, this course gives a nice net drop in elevation leading to a lot of PRs. With weather in the 40s, cloudy and a light breeze it was the perfect conditions to put up some fast splits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wanting to run a negative split race, I started out just ahead of the 1:45 pace group, thinking 1:40 would be a great finish for me based on my training leading up to the race. Perhaps what I didn&amp;rsquo;t anticipate is the power that on-course energy, adrenaline of a race, and the motivation to catch and pass pacers would carry me further than I thought.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By mile 5, I had caught the 1:40 pace group and we were approaching a familiar part of the course to me, Great Northern Boulevard, where I had done training runs. I had not done a great job tapering leading up to this race, having ran the Thursday prior to this Sunday race, but any remaining soreness from the slog of my training block had worn off and I was feeling in a groove. I chose to settle in and get comfortable in the middle miles. Thinking I would not catch the 1:35 group, I let the pace slip slightly from 7 minute miles as we started hitting some rolling hills.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s probably around mile 10 that I can see the 1:35 stick in the distance as we go up and down 45th. As we turned south I knew I had friends waiting around mile 11 to cheer me on, having not even seen them yet I was already drawing an energy boost from it in anticipation. By the time I had reached them, I was just behind the 1:35 pacer, with the group starting to take off ahead for a fast finish. I followed suit, turning down through UT&amp;rsquo;s campus (another familiar place from training runs), I could feel the impending finish line and started to empty the tank. With a couple tough uphill sections, I was able to turn in a 7 flat and a 6:50 for my final two splits.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;What blows my mind still is that over the course of my training I don&amp;rsquo;t think I turned in a single mile at a 7 minute pace. I did weekly speed/interval workouts (sometimes with hills), but never held a pace like that for a mile, maybe half that for a single repetition. It is still very counterintuitive to me that building weekly mileage at slower paces still sets you up for fast races like this. Conventional wisdom- or maybe common sense, might suggest that you actually run your goal paces during workouts. I have done so in anticipation of my goal &lt;em&gt;marathon&lt;/em&gt; pace, but was blown away by my endurance at a faster pace over a shorter distance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Completing this race has been a huge motivator to knock out my peak 50 mile week leading up to a taper for the Austin Marathon next month. While I will need to be conservative due to the fast nature of this course in predicting marathon distance times, I have absolutely had to adjust my goals for racing the marathon distance. Austin is notoriously a hilly (no, Texas is not all flat!) course, with an unrelenting climb north from miles 11 to 18 which will put my hill training sessions to the test, but this race has served its role as a barometer of my level of fitness nonetheless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When my first marathon is in the books I will crack open the training data captured on each run via my watch and do some discovery and analysis over this entire block. I may even spin up and host a dashboard for people to play around with, so check back with me soon!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Strava clout below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;strava-embed-placeholder&#34; data-embed-type=&#34;activity&#34; data-embed-id=&#34;10602567082&#34; data-style=&#34;standard&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;script src=&#34;https://strava-embeds.com/embed.js&#34;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
    <title>Coalesce Conference 2023: How Roche GTM Manages Multi-project dbt Deployments</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/coalesce-2023/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/coalesce-2023/</guid>
    <description>
        &lt;p&gt;I recently spoke at dbt labs&amp;rsquo; Coalesce Conference in San Diego! Alongside the Head of Engineering for the Roche Go-to-market Analytics Department, &lt;a href=&#34;https://ch.linkedin.com/in/yannick-misteli-b86129105&#34;&gt;Yannick Misteli&lt;/a&gt; and I discuss multi-project deployments of dbt to scale your analytics workflow. This talk precedes features that were announced at this Coalesce Conference around &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.getdbt.com/best-practices/how-we-mesh/mesh-1-intro&#34;&gt;dbt mesh&lt;/a&gt;, discussing how Roche managed model interaction between dbt projects before these features existed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can watch a recording of the talk below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&#34;766&#34; height=&#34;431&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Z4f04K4Ljlg?si=vf6JNTloD3oIV5_N&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you work for an analytics team thinking about adopting a multi-project architecture with dbt, I&amp;rsquo;m always happy to discuss your vision with you and offer insights having done this at scale. Comment below or reach out to me via tyler [at] tylerrouze.com!&lt;/p&gt;

    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
    <title>My First dbt-core Contribution!</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/first-dbt-core-contribution/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/first-dbt-core-contribution/</guid>
    <description>
        &lt;p&gt;I recently made my first &lt;code&gt;dbt-core&lt;/code&gt; open-source contribution! This contribution adds &lt;code&gt;unmodified&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;old&lt;/code&gt; &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.getdbt.com/reference/node-selection/methods#the-state-method&#34;&gt;state selection&lt;/a&gt; methods to the dbt CLI. The main motivation is to make it easy to exclude late-binding views from our dbt job&amp;rsquo;s DAG, reducing the runtime overhead. You can see some details that precipitated this contribution &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/dbt-labs/dbt-core/issues/7564&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can watch a short demo on the contribution below:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;iframe width=&#34;766&#34; height=&#34;431&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/RB6CxbQQ_YM?si=UDomcCa34LDSMJw7&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To take it for a spin yourself, you might run a command that excludes the intersection of views and unchanged models from the DAG:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;
&lt;table class=&#34;lntable&#34;&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;lnt&#34;&gt;1
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
&lt;td class=&#34;lntd&#34;&gt;
&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34; data-lang=&#34;bash&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;dbt run -s config.materialized:view,state:unmodified --state ./path/to/artifats
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you end up using this feature extension, I&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you! When I worked on this, I did it entirely inspired by the late-binding view use-case, but I&amp;rsquo;d be curious to hear how you put it to use in your dbt jobs. As always, reach out to me via tyler [at] tylerrouze.com or comment below!&lt;/p&gt;

    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
    <title>dbt Chicago Meetup - May 2023</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/dbt-meetup-chicago-may-23/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/dbt-meetup-chicago-may-23/</guid>
    <description>
        &lt;p&gt;I took the opportunity to share some insights about my experiences in scaling dbt development in the enterprise during the May 2023 dbt Chicago Meetup. You can see the slides below and picture of me speaking at the event below!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/chicago_meetup.jpeg&#34;&gt;
&lt;script type=&#34;text/javascript&#34; src= &#39;/js/pdf-js/build/pdf.js&#39;&gt;&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;style&gt;
  #embed-pdf-container {
    position: relative;
    width: 100%;
    height: auto;
    min-height: 20vh;
     
  }
  
  .pdf-canvas {
    border: 1px solid black;
    direction: ltr;
    width: 100%;
    height: auto;
    display: none;
  }
  
  #the-canvas {
    border: 1px solid black;
    direction: ltr;
    width: 100%;
    height: auto;
    display: none;
  }
  
  
  .pdf-loadingWrapper {
    display: none;
    justify-content: center;
    align-items: center;
    width: 100%;
    height: 350px;
  }
  
  .pdf-loading {
    display: inline-block;
    width: 50px;
    height: 50px;
    border: 3px solid #d2d0d0;;
    border-radius: 50%;
    border-top-color: #383838;
    animation: spin 1s ease-in-out infinite;
    -webkit-animation: spin 1s ease-in-out infinite;
  }
  
  
  
  
  
  #overlayText {
    word-wrap: break-word;
    display: grid;
    justify-content: end;
  }
  
  #overlayText a {
    position: relative;
    top: 10px;
    right: 4px;
    color: #000;
    margin: auto;
    background-color: #eeeeee;
    padding: 0.3em 1em;
    border: solid 2px;
    border-radius: 12px;
    border-color: #00000030;
    text-decoration: none;
  }
  
  #overlayText svg {
    height: clamp(1em, 2vw, 1.4em);
    width:  clamp(1em, 2vw, 1.4em);
  }
  
  
  
  @keyframes spin {
    to { -webkit-transform: rotate(360deg); }
  }
  @-webkit-keyframes spin {
    to { -webkit-transform: rotate(360deg); }
  }
  &lt;/style&gt;&lt;div class=&#34;embed-pdf-container&#34; id=&#34;embed-pdf-container-de2e3ca4&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;pdf-loadingWrapper&#34; id=&#34;pdf-loadingWrapper-de2e3ca4&#34;&gt;
        &lt;div class=&#34;pdf-loading&#34; id=&#34;pdf-loading-de2e3ca4&#34;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div id=&#34;overlayText&#34;&gt;
      &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/dbt_chicago_may_meetup.pdf&#34; aria-label=&#34;Download&#34; download&gt;
        &lt;svg aria-hidden=&#34;true&#34; xmlns=&#34;http://www.w3.org/2000/svg&#34; viewBox=&#34;0 0 18 18&#34;&gt;
            &lt;path d=&#34;M9 13c.3 0 .5-.1.7-.3L15.4 7 14 5.6l-4 4V1H8v8.6l-4-4L2.6 7l5.7 5.7c.2.2.4.3.7.3zm-7 2h14v2H2z&#34; /&gt;
        &lt;/svg&gt;
      &lt;/a&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;canvas class=&#34;pdf-canvas&#34; id=&#34;pdf-canvas-de2e3ca4&#34;&gt;&lt;/canvas&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;pdf-paginator&#34; id=&#34;pdf-paginator-de2e3ca4&#34;&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;pdf-prev-de2e3ca4&#34;&gt;Previous&lt;/button&gt;
    &lt;button id=&#34;pdf-next-de2e3ca4&#34;&gt;Next&lt;/button&gt; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;
    &lt;span&gt;
      &lt;span class=&#34;pdf-pagenum&#34; id=&#34;pdf-pagenum-de2e3ca4&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt; / &lt;span class=&#34;pdf-pagecount&#34; id=&#34;pdf-pagecount-de2e3ca4&#34;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;a class=&#34;pdf-source&#34; id=&#34;pdf-source-de2e3ca4&#34; href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/dbt_chicago_may_meetup.pdf&#34;&gt;[pdf]&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;noscript&gt;
View the PDF file &lt;a class=&#34;pdf-source&#34; id=&#34;pdf-source-noscript-de2e3ca4&#34; href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/dbt_chicago_may_meetup.pdf&#34;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.
&lt;/noscript&gt;

&lt;script type=&#34;text/javascript&#34;&gt;
    (function(){
    var url = &#39;\/images\/dbt_chicago_may_meetup.pdf&#39;;

    var hidePaginator = &#34;&#34; === &#34;true&#34;;
    var hideLoader = &#34;&#34; === &#34;true&#34;;
    var selectedPageNum = parseInt(&#34;&#34;) || 1;

    
    var pdfjsLib = window[&#39;pdfjs-dist/build/pdf&#39;];

    
    if (pdfjsLib.GlobalWorkerOptions.workerSrc == &#39;&#39;)
      pdfjsLib.GlobalWorkerOptions.workerSrc = &#34;http:\/\/localhost:1313\/&#34; + &#39;js/pdf-js/build/pdf.worker.js&#39;;

    
    var pdfDoc = null,
        pageNum = selectedPageNum,
        pageRendering = false,
        pageNumPending = null,
        scale = 3,
        canvas = document.getElementById(&#39;pdf-canvas-de2e3ca4&#39;),
        ctx = canvas.getContext(&#39;2d&#39;),
        paginator = document.getElementById(&#34;pdf-paginator-de2e3ca4&#34;),
        loadingWrapper = document.getElementById(&#39;pdf-loadingWrapper-de2e3ca4&#39;);


    
    showPaginator();
    showLoader();

    

    function renderPage(num) {
      pageRendering = true;
      
      pdfDoc.getPage(num).then(function(page) {
        var viewport = page.getViewport({scale: scale});
        canvas.height = viewport.height;
        canvas.width = viewport.width;

        
        var renderContext = {
          canvasContext: ctx,
          viewport: viewport
        };
        var renderTask = page.render(renderContext);

        
        renderTask.promise.then(function() {
          pageRendering = false;
          showContent();

          if (pageNumPending !== null) {
            
            renderPage(pageNumPending);
            pageNumPending = null;
          }
        });
      });

      
      document.getElementById(&#39;pdf-pagenum-de2e3ca4&#39;).textContent = num;
    }

    

    function showContent() {
      loadingWrapper.style.display = &#39;none&#39;;
      canvas.style.display = &#39;block&#39;;
    }

    

    function showLoader() {
      if(hideLoader) return
      loadingWrapper.style.display = &#39;flex&#39;;
      canvas.style.display = &#39;none&#39;;
    }

    

    function showPaginator() {
      if(hidePaginator) return
      paginator.style.display = &#39;block&#39;;
    }

    

    function queueRenderPage(num) {
      if (pageRendering) {
        pageNumPending = num;
      } else {
        renderPage(num);
      }
    }

    

    function onPrevPage() {
      if (pageNum &lt;= 1) {
        return;
      }
      pageNum--;
      queueRenderPage(pageNum);
    }
    document.getElementById(&#39;pdf-prev-de2e3ca4&#39;).addEventListener(&#39;click&#39;, onPrevPage);

    

    function onNextPage() {
      if (pageNum &gt;= pdfDoc.numPages) {
        return;
      }
      pageNum++;
      queueRenderPage(pageNum);
    }
    document.getElementById(&#39;pdf-next-de2e3ca4&#39;).addEventListener(&#39;click&#39;, onNextPage);

    

    pdfjsLib.getDocument(url).promise.then(function(pdfDoc_) {
      pdfDoc = pdfDoc_;
      var numPages = pdfDoc.numPages;
      document.getElementById(&#39;pdf-pagecount-de2e3ca4&#39;).textContent = numPages;

      
      if(pageNum &gt; numPages) {
        pageNum = numPages
      }

      
      renderPage(pageNum);
    });
    })();
&lt;/script&gt;

    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
    <title>Q&amp;A Session: What Does dbt Add to Databricks?</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/dbt-with-databricks/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/dbt-with-databricks/</guid>
    <description>
        &lt;iframe width=&#34;766&#34; height=&#34;431&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/Iiinevv_wn8?si=FY1vAtk7tWUP0BFY&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
    <title>How dbt Helps Our Clients Remove Data Engineering Bottlenecks</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/post/a8-dbt-webinar/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
    
    <guid>http://localhost:1313/post/a8-dbt-webinar/</guid>
    <description>
        &lt;iframe width=&#34;766&#34; height=&#34;431&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/uJgdkOWSsDo?si=7wNb0BByrjOV5Oki&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video player&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
